Right.
Obviously.
Okay. No.
我唔使，我唔使。
而動議嘅議案，我請毛孟靜議員發言及動議議案。
第二項議案，毛孟靜議員就譴責何君瑤議員以。
論終止待續議案所屬嘅事宜，交付調查委員會處理。
who habitually eat foreign sausages. Now that sort of lying.
now in Hong Kong we do have some racial and sexual bias laws under the Sex Discrimination Ordinance.
Now this misbehaviour is contained in the schedule and it's a quite a detailed account. I don't need to read out every word. Am I correct?
我清楚地記住，Mr. Kwok問這Mr. Ho要撤退或道歉或什麼，但Mr. Ho只是自己走了。
這個顧問會，根據《基本法》第797條，懲處Doctor Honorable Junius Ho for misbehaviour。
你會 expect一reasonable person，一reasonable person， considering all the circumstances of a particular incident taking place， would assume that
what we are talking about is at the meeting of the house committee on were in the middle of October. This doctor, honourable Junius Ho, in response to a statement I made, he said something like those.
was ruled by the person who was presiding over that presiding over that meeting, Mr Dennis Quirk to be sexually and racially harassing. It's obvious, and at the time I.
A racially different person, a woman or a gender different type of person, would get offended, would get insulted, would get intimidated. We're talking about reasonableness. All.
是。
The two ordinances protecting.
set legislative meeting.
conduct expected of a member of this legislature.
你 know more than full par at the
and he has seriously jeopardised the public's confidence in Lecceo.
now this the Junius Ho person as a member of Legco, has quite so obviously violated both ordinances.
It's a complete, a total lack of remorse for his conduct and his lied blatantly through his teeth. He has lied his face off.
now this reflected the sheer defiance, this person's sheer defiance of the rule of law, wanton abetment of sexual and racial harassment and lack of remorse.
If only this person, Mr Ho, would just say, "Oh, well, sorry, that's a slip of the tongue, and I didn't really mean anything." And if anyone gets offended, I do apologise. Things like that.
This would have gone away, but no, he argued in this most cheeky and blatantly unremorseful manner. So this person, Junius Ho, has to be censured. Thank you.
性與 racial rights， and he made this remark towards female members of the Legislative Council. Please note the plural and made them feel offended and insulted.
And this, well, according to the records, subsequently, this Junius Ho still argue that his remark carried no implication whatsoever of sex discrimination or offending women.
我唔係要講長，我唔係要講十五分鐘。係，明顯對任何一個有理的人，呢個詹俊豪嘅講話係完全違反咗整體同。
Now of course I understand Mr Ho has also suffered fairly gravely as a result of his babbling but racial and sexist racist and sexist remark at this legislature to the point that his alma mater.
Some university in the UK, Anglia Ruskin University, has decided to strip his doctorate degree. That's a huge price to pay for one big.
第三項議案，容海欣議員就顯。
議案所屬嘅事宜，交付調查委員會處理。
按照議事規則第四十九B.2A條，辯論中止待續。
現在嘅待議議題係毛孟靜議員嘅議案，予以通過。